Besides the methods shown in the previous video,
除了在上个视频中演示的方法之外
I've added two more methods to the Gaussian class.
我还向 Gaussian 类添加了两个方法
These are the add method and the repr or representation method.
分别是 add 和 repr (represent 的缩写 意思是表现)
These are both called magic methods.
它们都称为魔术方法
The syntax might look somewhat familiar
看起来熟悉吗？
because you've actually already worked with a magic method.
是的 因为你已经用过一个魔术方法 即 init 方法
The init function which initializes a new object is a magic method.
init 方法是一个魔术方法 负责初始化新的对象
Magic methods let you override and customize default Python behavior.
魔术方法使你能够重写和自定义默认 Python 行为
For example, the init method lets you customize how Python instantiates an object.
例如 init 方法使你能够自定义 Python 实例化对象的方式
The add method overrides the behavior of the plus sign.
add 方法会重写加号的行为
I'm going to execute the code cell with the Gaussian class.
我将执行包含 Gaussian 类的代码单元格
Below, I've instantiated two Gaussian objects,
我在这里实例化了两个 Gaussian 对象
and then I add them together.
然后将它们加到一起
Python knows how to add two floats together or two integers together.
Python 知道如何将两个浮点数或整数相加
These operations are defined as part of a Python installation.
这些运算在 Python 安装包中已经定义好了
Adding a Gaussian to a Gaussian, however,
但是将 Gaussian 与 Gaussian 相加
has no meaning in Python,
在 Python 中没有任何意义
so this code should produce an error. I'm going to run it.
因此这段代码应该产生报错 我运行下看看
Well, the code didn't produce an error.
代码没有产生报错
That's because I've defined the behavior of adding two Gaussian together.
这是因为我定义了将两个高斯函数相加的行为
Scrolling back up to the add magic method,
向上滚动到 add 魔术方法部分
you can see how this works.
看看它的原理
The function has two inputs, self and other.
该函数有两个输入 分别是 self 和 other
Self refers to the object to the left of the plus sign.
self 是指加号左边的对象
Other refers to the object on the right side of the plus sign.
other 是指加号右侧的对象
I can then define what it means to add these two objects together.
然后定义将这两个对象相加的含义
Adding two Gaussian together sums the means together and
将两个 Gaussian 相加是指对均值求和
takes the square root of the squares of the standard deviations.
并计算标准偏差平方和的平方根
Then the code instantiates
然后代码用新的均值和新的标准偏差
a new Gaussian object with the new mean and the new standard deviation,
实例化一个新的 Gaussian 对象
and returns the new object.
并返回该新对象
For another example, consider the representation method.
再来看看 repr 方法
In Python, do you remember what happens when the only code on a line is a variable?
在 Python 中 如果一行代码只有一个变量 会怎样？
Python will print out the value of the variable.
Python 将输出该变量的值
So, if I say x=5,
假设 x=5
and then just execute x. Python prints out the value of five.
仅运行 x  Python 将输出值 5
The representation magic method controls what gets printed out.
repr 方法会控制输出内容
So here, the code overrides
这段代码重写了
the default representation behavior to print out
默认的 repr 行为
the mean and standard deviation of the Gaussian object.
输出 Gaussian 对象的均值和标准偏差
Here, I'm going to run this line of code so you can see the results.
我将运行这行代码并看看结果如何
Python has dozens of magic methods.
Python 有几十个魔术方法
You can override the plus sign, minus sign, division,
你可以重写加号 减号 除号
multiplication, greater than, and less than symbols just to give a few more examples.
乘号 大于 小于符号 等等
To get practice with magic methods,
为了练习使用魔术方法
you'll go back to the Gaussian method and rewrite the code you've just seen.
你将回到 Gaussian 方法并重新编写刚刚查看的代码
If you're getting tired of rewriting code, not to worry.
如果你已经厌烦了重新编写代码 别担心
Soon, you'll be converting this Gaussian module into
很快你会将此 Gaussian 模块转换成实际软件包
an actual package and then adding more functionality.
然后添加更多功能